A thrilling road trip comedy.
The Family Plan is a action, comedy, family film directed by Simon Cellan Jones.
Dan Morgan is many things: a devoted husband, a
loving father, a celebrated car salesman.
He's also a former assassin.
And when his past catches up to his present, he's forced to take his
unsuspecting family on a road trip unlike any other.
Dan Morgan, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Jessica Morgan, played by Michelle Monaghan.
Gwen, played by Maggie Q.
Nina Morgan, played by Zoe Colletti.
Kyle Morgan, played by Van Crosby.
McCaffrey, played by Ciarán Hinds.
The Family Plan is a 2023 American action comedy film starring Mark Wahlberg as a suburban car salesman who goes
on the run with his unsuspecting family when his secret past as a government assassin is exposed.
The film also stars Michelle Monaghan, Zoe Colletti, Van
Crosby, Saïd Taghmaoui, Maggie Q, and Ciarán Hinds.
It is directed by Simon Cellan Jones and written by David Coggeshall.
Apple Studios began production in late 2022.
The film was released by Apple TV+ on December 15, 2023.
It received generally negative reviews, but became
most-viewed on the platform for a brief time.
A sequel, The Family Plan 2, was released on November 21, 2025.
The film explores themes of road trip, on the run,
gamer, car salesman, las vegas.
The tone is lighthearted and uplifting.